

AHMED ABBASSI

Software Engineering Student

- @ a.abbassi21306@pi.tn
- **J** +216 23-631-633
- Tunis, Tunisia

- in ahmed-abbassi-
- 3ibsi69

SKILLS



JavaScript Python

Microsoft Word (SQL

Microsoft Excel | PLSQL

LateX

Linux

CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Word (office 2016)

Microsoft Excel (office 2016)

ABOUT ME

I'm a 21 years old student seeking opportunities to apply my knowledge and skills in a real-world setting, and eager to contribute to innovative projects that make a positive impact. I hope to bring the best out of myself and work within a well-communicated team.

EXPERIENCE

Part-time Sales Associate | Decathlon

10/06/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | Karriery

= 29/05/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | B and smile

i 01/08/2022 - 31/08/2022

Tunis, Tunisia

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native

English: Intermediate / B2

French: Intermediate / B1

Software Engineering | Polytech INTL

iii 09 2021 - Present

EDUCATION

Tunis, Tunisia

Tunis, Tunisia

Computer Science Baccalaureate | Rue de Russie High School

PROJECTS

= 09 2020 - 05 2021

Portfolio Website 🖸

OILIOIIO VVEDSILE

i 05/06/2023 - 08/06/2023

• [HTML] CSS] SCSS] JavaScript

Clinic site for booking (7)

i 02/02/2023 - 03/16/2023

• (HTML)(CSS)(Javascript)(Php)

Portfolio Website (React) 😱

21/06/2023 - 22/06/2023

• React HTML CSS SCSS JavaScript

To Do-list 😱

- **12/06/2023**
- [HTML] (CSS) [Javascript]

INTERESTS

Gaming

Music

Sports

Search tool 🜎

- ****** 05/01/2023 05/09/2023
- Python

Gestion de stock

- **1** 01-2022 02-2022
- (C)